Kannawa-san. Kamegawa-kun.
May I speak with you two?
A drinking party, you say?
Yup.
Yamaga-san from our office
is getting married soon.
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Wow, that's wonderful.
Married... H-How wonderful...
That reminds me... Mom called sayin' she
had someone she wanted to introduce me to...
You know how we haven't held a welcome
party for you yet, Kamegawa-kun?
That's why I'd like us to merge
the celebration of the marriage
and your employment into one drinking party.
Thank you so much!
Now, there's a reason why
I specifically called for you two.
I want to ask you, Kamegawa-kun,
to organize the party.
What? Me?
I think it'd be beneficial for the newbie
to use this experience to learn
how to entertain guests.
I-I see.
Kannawa-san, be sure to
lend him a hand on this.
- Show him some good restaurants.
- Yes, sir.
Like I would know any good spots!
I never go to places where people socialize!
Can I also ask you two to choose
a gift for the happy couple?
Understood.
It's hard enough to find a restaurant,
and now he wants me to pick a gift, too?!
I'm so glad.
I look forward to what
you'll have in store for us!
Let's start with the marriage celebration.
Follow me!
I'll be in your care!
MY AWKWARD SENPAI
"I Gotta Support the Drinking Party's Organizer!"
Wow. There are so many to look at.
But what do people usually give
their coworkers as a wedding gift?
Ceremonial occasions, including gift-giving,
are fundamental to being a member of society.
- Leave it to me.
- Yes, ma'am!
Is what I said...
but I honestly have no clue what to give
someone who's gettin' married!
- This looks good.
- My years of being introverted are biting me...
The wedding's just around the corner now!
Wait, is Kannawa-san going?
Nah, she wasn't invited.
I bet she'd just say something like,
"Weddings are just for the self-satisfaction
of the people involved."
I haven't gone to a wedding, let alone organized...
- Even just plates come in so many types!
- But I need to support my junior!
Something they'd enjoy, but that's
appropriate for a member of society...
This looks nice.
That cat pattern...
So cute...
Oh? Matching mugs?
Would something like that do the trick?
- I-I'm sorry. It's because I startled you...
- No...
Is anyone hurt?
No, we're fine.
I've gone and done it now...
My apologies. Please, let me pay for that.
No, please...
It's all right. Don't worry about it.
But I can't just leave like this. Let me at least—
In that case, do you have
more of these in the back?
Oh, yes, we do...
What a relief.
- I was just thinking about getting the pair.
- Hey, Kamegawa—
In that case, I'll bring them out immediately.
Hey, wait!
If you're only buying them
because of me, don't!
It's not like that!
I really thought those were great mugs.
I want to use them myself,
so I'm buying them for myself.
Well, I'm going to go buy them.
Hey, wait a minute!
Then at least let me buy them for you!
It's for me, so I'll pay for them.
No, no!
No, no, no...
I'm so ashamed...
I need to do better for the next
gift-buying opportunity.
It's time for me to awaken my search skills
from my years of obsessing over games!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I've thought of a present.
- Let's go.
- Yes, ma'am!
Thanks to you, we got a great gift!
Thank you, Senpai.
I didn't do much advising.
This towel is super-duper soft.
I hope they like it.
But I was surprised to learn you
take your coffee black, Senpai.
Adding things like sugar
would dilute the original flavor.
- It's improper.
- Is that so?
I feel like it tastes better,
even with just a little...
No need.
Wh-Why am I bein' pointlessly pretentious?
I guess, to coffee aficionados, it's improper...
But it tastes good this way.
I'm so jealous.
But when I was a newbie,
Senpai always took her coffee black.
I also need to...
Coffee is simply meant to
keep you awake. That's all.
I see.
You eat sweets a lot,
so I just assumed you'd prefer...
Should I bring you sugar or milk?
- Bring both...
- Yes, ma'am!
Delicious. But this is so embarrassing...
You got this, me!
I need to be a better senpai in front of him.
Next, we need to find our venue.
Right!
We need to make reservations quickly,
since it's just before Golden Week.
Yes, ma'am!
But I don't know a lot about venues...
TOP IZAKAYAS FOR LARGE GROUPS
I wonder if Kamegawa has
any places he frequents.
Does he prefer beer? Japanese sake?
He could be a wine kind of guy.
I wonder what everyone would like...
- I think Hita-san would want to eat a lot.
- I don't know nothin' about Kamegawa.
Just that he likes model kits and
had to cut back on his lunch money.
- Senpai?
- What about you?
Do you like drinking?
Me? Nah, it's not really my thing.
I see!
Shoot! I got careless because we're the same...
Yeah, alcohol tastes better when you
drink with people you like to be with.
No need to push yourself.
Really?
I feel better after hearing that.
Um, I'm sorry you got dragged
into organizing this with me.
Where's this coming from?
I heard that you don't usually
go to drinking parties.
Don't worry about it.
It's for a celebratory event
and your welcome party.
Of course I'll attend.
I appreciate it.
No worries.
Well...
If you get invited by a senior in the future,
you should decline if you don't want to go.
Yes, ma'am!
But...
I'd like to go out drinking with you, Senpai.
There'd be no point in drinking with you.
You're right.
What the heck am I sayin'?!
After Kamegawa invited me?!
But it just came outta nowhere...
Th-That's enough!
Let's hurry and find a venue!
Oh, uh, right!
We picked out a present and made
a restaurant reservation, but...
Why did I turn him down that way?!
It makes it awkward for me
to ever invite him out to drink!
What'll I do?!
Isn't this yesterday's...
Oh, good morning!
Oh, uh, morning.
So... what's this about?
Ah, well, you see...
After I went home, I realized a guy
living alone really only needs one mug.
Besides...
It looked like you really
liked that mug, Senpai.
It's a token of my gratitude
for helping me out yesterday.
Please use it, if you'd like.
I'll use it as a toothbrush holder.
A toothbrush holder?!
IZAKAYA MATSUZAKA
- Kannawa-san, lead the toast!
- Yeah!
I'm not going to put on a show.
If you have any complaints,
take them to the chief for making me do this.
Congrats on the marriage and to the new hire.
- Cheers.
- Cheers!
- Is that allowed?!
I should have known. My bad.
I'm so happy to drink with you, Kannawa-san!
This is how the seating
was arranged, so I suppose so.
Thanks for taking on all those tasks for us.
It's my duty.
Now, drink up!
Oh, allow me.
My, oh, my!
What a pleasure to have
Kannawa-san pour me a drink!
I wonder if he's doin' all right...
- Yo! Is Kannawa's newbie holding up well?
- Y-Yes!
So, are you getting along with her?
Yes, I think so.
I was worried, since the newbies
are always scared of her.
I... I see...
- I'm really happy for you, Yamaga-kun.
- Thank you!
I, for one, appreciate that she's been
honest about my mistakes and flaws,
and that she corrects me.
- Well said, newbie!
- O-Ouch!
And when you're so young! Impressive!
Here, drink up. We can let loose today!
B-But I don't really...
Nonsense! Here!
Th-Then...
Huh?
Senpai?
Hey—
Um, Kannawa?
- I'm testing this for poison.
- What?
I'm his mentor!
I can't have him drinking things
without knowing what's in them!
What a scary mentor.
That's the spirit, Kannawa! Drink some more!
I'm so glad to be able to
drink with you, Kannawa.
Yeah...
Hey, hey.
Try this, too.
Thank you so much.
C'mon, I don't see you drinking.
You can just drink this!
There you go again!
Kamegawa can't enjoy himself
if you keep acting like this.
Let's take it easy.
I'm going to the bathroom...
Senpai's taking a long time...
I hope she's okay.
I feel sick...
Senpai!
Are you oka—
No problems here!
Sorry...
I'm not feeling too well.
I'll head home first.
Oh, of course!
I'll go get your stuff.
I appreciate it.
What?!
Kannawa-san's going home?
But she finally went out with us!
Say something, Chief!
Hey, newbie.
You're the star of the show tonight!
Stay with us.
Let's get wasted!
S-Sure.
- But let me take Senpai her belongings...
- Kamegawa!
I just got word from that one project.
What exactly did you do?
"Th-That one project"?
Oh! That project! Of course!
I'm sorry. I need to head out, as well.
Aw, work?
Please excuse me!
I apologize.
Huh?
I made an unnecessary scene...
Not at all!
In fact, drinking parties were never really
my thing, so you helped me out.
I see.
Oh, Senpai!
Oh, no... Are you okay?
Let's sit down for a bit.
Hey.
- I'm a scary mentor, right?
- Huh?
What brought that on?
During the party...
you looked nervous the whole time.
I thought... it was because I was there...
and I scared you.
Not at all.
I admit I was nervous, since it was
my first time at an office drinking party,
but it wasn't your fault.
Is that so?
I heard it's good to take deep
breaths when you're nervous.
You're not a scary mentor at all, Senpai.
You've been very kind ever since
the first time I met you.
Um...
"The reason I applied to
your company is because..."
Are you nervous?
Think of interviews as a way
to see someone's personality.
You'll accomplish nothing by just repeating
the fancy speeches you memorized.
Y-You're right.
I heard it's good
to take deep breaths when you're nervous.
The one who's always being
considerate is you, Senpai.
Senpai! Actually, I'd still like to go out
drinking with you sometime.
I'm sorry.
I know you already declined.
Okay.
Huh?
Let's go. The two of us.
There are a lot of things I want to teach you,
and things I want to learn from you, too!
Yes, ma'am!...Senpai?
Oh, no!
Why would you chug so much beer
when you're such a lightweight?
Get a hold of yourself, Senpai!
Senpai!
Hey, you.
At least take a bath.
I'm sorry.
After I sent you home in the taxi last night,
I missed the last train.
I spent the night at a friend's place and
passed out, and then came straight here.
Oh, um... I apologize about that.
Oh, no. It's no problem!
What was I doin'?
Gettin' drunk and causin' trouble
for my junior like that?
Huh?
Is it just me, or does that look like
a lipstick stain on his shirt?
He said he spent the night
at a friend's place, but...
Could it be that he was with his girlfriend?
Wait.What's it to me if he has a girlfriend?
Senpai?
- Whoa! Coming in with lipstick on your shirt?
- What?
You said "friend," but I bet
it was a woman, right?
He did it! He asked the big question!
Oh, no. It's not that.
- This is—
- Now, now. No need to hide it.
I didn't know you were so
smooth, Kamegawa-kun.
Ah, wait...
Wh-What do I do?
Am I supposed to press him further?
But I think that'd be overstepping
into my junior's private life.
- Do you—
- No, like I was saying...
I got this stain when I helped
you into the taxi last night.
- What?
- I tried to get it off, but I couldn't.
H-H-H-Hurry up and throw that thing away!
But I don't have another to change into!
Go buy one! I'll pay for it!
What?! Wait, stop tugging!
Hurry and take it off!
Kannawa-san. Kamegawa-kun.
Come over here, please.
How can we help you?
Well, you see...
I'm sorry to ask you to do
this during Golden Week,
but would the two of you go to Okinawa for me?
Okinawa?!